Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audiovisual Collection, 1953-2015 and undated RL.00734
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Optical Media (CDs, DVDs), 1993-2015; undated; 4
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Color Showdown awards video, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0414)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Color Showdown case study, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0415)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Color Showdown case study agency and new business version, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0416)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk credentials 2-minute version, 2006 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0417)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk credentials 4-minute version, 2006 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0418)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk credentials 8-minute version, 2006 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0419)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Full Collection TV, Viral and Web 29 spots, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0420)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Hair Off; Outline; Tease, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0421)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Lovebites WalMart episodes 180a, 182a, 182, 2006 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0422)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Out of Home Philadelphia shoot 1-4 tape 1, 2006 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0423)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Out of Home Philadelphia shoot 1-4 tape 2, 2006 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0424)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk styling videos for Web, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0425)
  - JWTwo--Super Bowl 2011, 65 spots (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0426)
  - JWTwo--TBS and Internet Batch C online, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0427)
  - JWTwo--The Beta-7 Experience, 2005 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0428)
  - JWTwo--The Beta-7 Experience full version 11:00, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0429)
  - JWTwo--Tick Tock montage, 2010 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0430)
  - JWTwo--Today Show, Kleenex Let It Out Olympics segment, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0431)
  - JWTwo--Tom Doctoroff interview, Financial Times, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0432)
  - JWTwo--Tom Doctoroff on America's Nightly Scoreboard, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0433)
  - JWTwo--Tribute for Sir Martin Sorrell, 2009 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0434)
  - JWTwo--Trident, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0435)
  - JWTwo--Trident 2005-2007, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0436)
  - JWTwo--Ty Montague CNN News Super Bowl, 2009 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0437)
  - JWTwo--Visine spots 4a, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0438)
  - JWTwo--Visine spots 4b, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0439)
  - JWTwo--Visine spots 1a, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0440)
  - JWTwo--Vodafone videos, 2009 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0441)
  - JWTwo--Welch's Goodnnight Sleep, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0442)
  - JWTwo--WNBC Today Show, Ann Mack, 2010 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0443)
  - JWTwo--WPP Brand Pioneer video, Stuart Mickle 1:40, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0444)
  - JWTwo--WPP Strategy Presentation, Craig Davis reel, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0445)
  - JWTwo--Wyeth audio boards, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0446)
  - JWTwo--Wyeth My Menopause, Whoohoo, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0447)
  - JWTwo--Wyeth non-branded audio boards, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0448)
  - JWTwo--Wyeth Pristiq, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0449)
  - JWTwo--Wyeth Thermostat, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0450)
  - JWTwo--Wyeth unbranded animatics, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0451)
  - JWTwo--Wyeth unbranded, My Neurotransmitters, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0452)
  - JWTwo--Yes Virginia animation video (Macy's); Billy Collins Sundance titanium case study, 2009 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0453)
  - JWTwo--Zyrtec banners, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0454)
  - K, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0455)
  - K, 2009 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0456)
  - K, 1974 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0457)
  - K, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0458)
  - Kraft--Philly, Cheesy, Chili and Ritz data CD backup, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0459)
  - Kraft--Pre-Game Show mix from Hoffman Sound, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0460)
  - Learning to Love Risk CD-A, 2003 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0461)
  - Learning to Love Risk CD-B, 2003 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0462)
  - Life and Times of Stanley B. and Helen L. Resor 82:00, 2006 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0463)
  - Lovebites EPK P2 Cam, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0464)
  - Lovebites Season 2 critics' reel (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0465)
  - Macy's Believe Integrated, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0466)
  - Macy's Believe Mailboxes, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0467)
  - Macy's Believe Sponsorhip, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0468)
  - Macy's Come Together Fundraiser PR event, 2009 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0469)
  - Macy's Morning, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0470)
  - Macy's Believe Camp, 2011 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0471)
  - Managing Brands in Times of Crisis: Learning from 9/11; Findings from an agency study, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0472)
  - Mavericks at Work launch party, 2006 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0473)
  - Maverick book party, 2006 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0474)
  - Microsoft--Sean Durfy/Westjet/CRM, 2008 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0475)
  - Microsoft--Robert McKnight/QuickSilver; Katie Bayne/Coke; Eric Ryan/Method, 2009 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0476)
  - Mpower Intro: Mike Bloomberg and Bill Gates, 2008 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0477)
  - My First Book event, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0478)
  - Nestle Key Brand Review reel 1, 2008 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0479)
  - Nestle Key Brand Review reel 2, 2008 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0479)
  - NY Cares_2008 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0480)
  - New York Headquarters images, 2009 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0481)
  - New York Office best of reel (new hires video): Lipton, Kellogg's; DC Shoes, DTC; Smirnoff; Qwest; Merrill Lynch; Lever; Domino's; HSBC; Vaseline; Wild Aid, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0482)
  - Oakland Hills 08 PGA, 2008 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0483)
  - Panchera, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0484)
  - Passion: The Best Television JWT North America (disc to accompany book of same title), 2002 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0485)
  - Planning team, 2006 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0486)
  - Open Space photographs, 2005 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0487)
  - Open Space pictures, 2005 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0488)
  - Project: Pristiq (Stark Naked Productions), 2007 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0489)
  - Pull Up a Chair: CBS News Sunday Morning, 2009 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0490)
  - Quint and Vectoria, PC Format, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0491)
  - Review Ace, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0492)
  - RI/LA/London pictures, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0493)
  - RI/LA/London pictures, 2007 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0494)
  - Rio de Janeiro--2Q Creative, 2000 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0495)
  - RMG Connect Summary, 2008 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0496)
  - Rolaids, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0497)
  - Rolex--Ashes and Snow case study, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0498)
  - Rolex--Ashes and Snow supporting materials, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0499)
  - Rolex Heritage, 2009 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0500)
  - Rosemarie's 5th Anniversary Party 20:00, 2008 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0501)
  - Royal Birkdale 2008 British Open, Stephen Szurlej (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0502)
  - Service Member Dinner, BWF, 2009 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0503)
  - Shell GTL campaign, 2008 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0504)
  - Sierra On-Line--Caesar II, 1995 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0505)
  - Smirnoff Ice Radio [disc missing], Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0506)
  - Smirnoff Ice Radio, 2007 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0507)
  - Sony Ericsson WTA Tour year end video, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0508)
  - South X Southwest party favorite photos, 2012 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0509)
  - South X Southwest party remaining photos, 2012 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0510)
  - Squirrel Tales (Domino's) vol. 1-3, 2007 (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0511)
  - Stouffer's TV commercials, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0512)
  - Sweet Louise Sampler: The Sounds of ATX, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0513)
  - SYFH pictures No. 1, Undated (Box O7, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0514)
  - TASTE: A Cultural Journey into Sound CD collection--Masar: El 'Aysh Wel Melh, 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0515)
  - TASTE: A Cultural Journey into Sound CD collection--Bassem Rizk: Echoes from a Past, 2004 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0516)
  - TASTE: A Cultural Journey into Sound CD collection--Mohsen Subhi: Mawasem, 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0517)
  - TASTE: A Cultural Journey into Sound CD collection--Sign of Thyme: Like All People, 2005 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0518)
  - TASTE: A Cultural Journey into Sound CD collection--Hewarj I 97: 9 Days of Solitude The Damascus Session, 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0519)
  - TASTE: A Cultural Journey into Sound CD collection--El Dor el Awal: Qarar Izala, 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0520)
  - TASTE: A Cultural Journey into Sound CD collection--Ziad El Ahmadie meets Fun Jan Shai: the Project Beyond Traditions, 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0521)
  - TASTE: A Cultural Journey into Sound CD collection--Andre Msane: Souffle d'Orient, 2004 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0522)
  - TASTE: A Cultural Journey into Sound CD collection--Riad Abdel-Gawad: El Tarab El Aseel, 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0523)
  - The Boardroom JWT, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0524)
  - The Park--Invasion of the Bulls, 2008 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0525)
  - Ton O., Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0526)
  - TWC Kraft/Nabisco DVD-1, 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0527)
  - Twit TV data disc, 2011 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0528)
  - UNILA, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0529)
  - UNILA--Presentation, 2003 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0530)
  - UNILA--2003 Q3RF and 2004 Budget; Tom O'Connell, Jose M. Yunis (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0531)
  - UNILA--2003 Q3RF and 2004 Budget; Tom O'Connell, Jose M. Yunis (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0532)
  - UNILA--2004 HPC Fee v.02 Euros (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0533)
  - UNILA--2004 HPC Fee v.7.1 Euros (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0534)
  - Unilever--Communication Channel Planning Instrumental to Success, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0535)
  - Unilever Scope--Communication Channel Planning Instrumental to Success, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0536)
  - Unilever--Hit the High Notes Advanced Brand Communication, ABC Jazz Compilation CD, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0537)
  - Unilever--Hit the High Notes Advanced Brand Communication, Presentation Materials, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0538)
  - Ultimate Kit Kat Break viral video, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0539)
  - Valhalla 08 Ryder Cup, Stephen Szurlej, 2008 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0540)
  - VMS--Alpha Moms, Good Morning America ABC national, 2007 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0541)
  - VMS--Bob Jeffrey, Infocus Bloomberg national, 2007 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0542)
  - VMS--Clarity episode, Colbert Report, Comedy Central national, 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0543)
  - VMS--JWT liquor spots aired: Absolut, Grey Goose, Stolichnaya, Belvedere, Bacardi, Rums of Puerto Rico, Patron, 2007 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0544)
  - VMS--JetBlue, Situation Room, CNN, 2009 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0545)
  - VMS--Marion Salzman: Fox News; BBC America; CNBC, 2006-2007 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0546)
  - VMS--Outside the Lines Issue of Child Support, ESPN, 2009 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0547)
  - VMS--Paul Reiser, AM Northwest KATU-TV Portland Ore., 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0548)
  - VMS--Paul Reiser: WB2DAY, KWGN-TV Denver; KTLA Morning News, Los Angeles; WB Morning News, KSWB-TV San Diego; Am Northwest, KATU-TV Portland, 2006 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0549)
  - Wilkinson Sword--Fight for Kisses, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0550)
  - WooHoo Original, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0551)
  - World War II from Space; History Channel, 2012 (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0552)
  - Worldwide Creative Council Meeting: Kenco; Special Olympics, Undated (Box O8, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0553)
  - WWCE Shot List MPEG, 2000 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0554)
  - WPP reel CJ, Undated (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0555)
  - Wyeth Audioboard, 2007 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0556)
  - Wyeth Audioboard, 2007 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0557)
  - [not used] (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0558)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JWT Global Reel for Johnson and Johnson, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0559)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JWT Global Reel for Johnson and Johnson, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0560)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JWT Global Reel for Johnson and Johnson, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0561)
  - Audiovisual Binder--WPP Meeting, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0562)
  - Audiovisual Binder--TV spots for WPP Meeting, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0563)
  - Audiovisual Binder--WPP Meeting, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0564)
  - Audiovisual Binder--LA reel, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0565)
  - Audiovisual Binder--LA reel 2, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0566)
  - Audiovisual Binder--DTC Integrated campaign-Cannes, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0567)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Burt Manning reel, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0568)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Burt Manning reel, Undated (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0569)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Recruitment, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0570)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Recruitment DR, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0571)
  - Audiovisual Binder--FCD meeting, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0572)
  - Audiovisual Binder--ECD meeting, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0573)
  - Audiovisual Binder--ECD Walt version, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0574)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Q2-Q1 combined, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0575)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JWT radio intern demo, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0576)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Best before 2006 film (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0577)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Best before 2006 film (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0578)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Atlanta meeting: HSBC, DTC presentations, 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0579)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Atlanta meeting, 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0580)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Ty Montague reel: Nike, 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0581)
  - Audiovisual Binder--DC Shoes, 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0582)
  - Audiovisual Binder--New York montage, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0583)
  - Audiovisual Binder--New York sports spots, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0584)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Ty Montague reel: Jordan XIII, 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0585)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Ty Montague reel: Brand Jordan, 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0586)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Jeep; Honda; Tyson Chicken, 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0587)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Teddybears advance CD, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0588)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Hurra Torpedo: The Crushing Blow titanium submission long version, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0589)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JWT 11 spots, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0590)
  - [not used] (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0591)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Splash website movie, Undated (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0592)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Spashingsurprise.com Trident website, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0593)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Ty Montague various works, Undated (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0594)
  - [not used] (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0595)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JetBlue Town Hall, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0596)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Halls spots, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0597)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Ty Montague various works, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0598)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Ty Montague various works, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0599)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Cheese Nips; Halls; Beerka, 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0600)
  - Audiovisual Binder--12 spots, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0601)
  - Audiovisual Binder--Sundance Channel Action Poetry Series, 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0602)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JWT Global Creative Challenge Q2 All TV Scoring 5, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0603)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JWT Global Creative Challenge Q2 All TV Scoring 6 and Above, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0604)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JWT Worldwide 2005 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0605)
  - Audiovisual Binder--JWT Global Creative Challenge Q2 All TV Scoring 5, 2006 (Box O9, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0606)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Cannes Lions 2010; Disc 1: Film, Young Lions, Special Awards (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0607)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Cannes Lions 2010; Disc 2: Film Craft, Jury, Special Awards (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0608)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Cannes Lions 2010; Disc 3: Press, Outdoor, Radio, Titanium, Special Awards, Highlights of the Week; All Winners (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0609)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Cannes Lions 2010; Disc 4: Direct, Media, Promo, Cyber, Design, PR (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0610)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes Top 15, 2011 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0611)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Unilever Seminar, 2011 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0612)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0613)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Tradittional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0614)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0615)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0616)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Traditional Master, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0617)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0618)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Radio DVD, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0619)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ford Everybody In, 2009 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0620)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0621)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0622)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Traditional Master, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0623)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0624)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0625)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Best of Reel, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0626)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0627)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Traditional, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0628)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT 18 spots, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0629)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0630)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0631)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0632)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0633)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Network Award Wins, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0634)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Worldwide Creative Council 6s or Better, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0635)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Worldwide Creative Council 6s or Better, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0636)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Worldwide Creative Council 6s or Better, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0637)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Worldwide Creative Council 6s or Better, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0638)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ty Town Hall Video, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0639)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Best of Reel, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0640)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Best of Reel, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0641)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Best of Reel, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0642)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Best of the Best, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0643)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--New Case Studies and Presentation Video, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0644)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes 2008 Submission Master (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0645)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--PR Loop, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0646)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ty Town Hall Video, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0647)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--DTC, Kleenex, JetBlue, Sunsilk, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0648)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--2008 Current Creative Work (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0649)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--HSBC, Ford, End Meth, Kleenex, DTC, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0650)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Smirnoff, Sunsilk, Halls, Stride, Kimberly Clark, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0651)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ty Town Hall Video, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0652)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ty Town Hall Video, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0653)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ty Town Hall Video, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0654)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Lauren LaFranz: Chipotle, Idea, Lynx, Listerine, Jacobs Momente, Milko Survival Guide, Wilkinson Sword, Undated (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0655)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--European Creative Challenge, Undated (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0656)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes Lions, 2011 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0657)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--We Made: JWT MEA Micro Case Studies, Undated (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0658)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Best 10: GSS, Pepsi, Nike, Set Max, Kurkure, Nokia, Birla Sunlife, Goodknight, Undated (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0659)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Pepsi Out of Home, Lux, HSBC, 2006 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0660)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Boards Submission November, 2006 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0661)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0662)